Spalek, John M.; Papers ger106
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Tape Recordings, 1976-2010; 1
  - KUHLENBECK, HARTWIG - Interview with Doris Bartuska about Kuhlenbeck. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 November 8 (Cassette 201)
  - KUHNELT-LEDDIHN, ERIK VON, 1974 December (Cassette 202)
  - LACHMAN, FREDERICK - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 January 5 (Cassette 203)
  - LAHN, ILSE - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 August 3 (Cassette 204)
  - LANDAU, ANNELIESE, 1982 December 29 (Cassette 205)
  - LANDSBERG, ERIKA SUZANNE - Interview with Kora Dalager, primarily about her mother, Erika Suzanne Landsberg., 2008 May 3 (Cassette 206)
  - LANDSBERG, HELMUT ERICH, Undated (Cassette 207)
  - LANDSHOFF, FRITZ, Undated (Cassette 208)
  - LANDSHOFF, ROLF - Interview with Ruth Landshoff about her father, Rolf., 2005 August 28 (Cassette 209)
  - LANDVER, ROSE, Undated (Cassette 210)
  - LANTZ, ROBERT - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1977 November 8; 1989 August 10 (Cassette 211)
  - LAQUEUR, GERT LUDWIG, 1981 January 29 (Cassette 212)
  - LAVINE, RUTH - Interview with Ruth Lavine about her life., 1996 March 5 (Cassette 213)
  - LEBORG, REGINALD - Interview with Regina Leborg about her father, Reginald. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 June 8 (Cassette 214)
  - LEDERER, EMIL - Interview with Gertrud Lederer about her husband, Emil., 1979 July 18 (Cassette 215)
  - LEDERER, FRANZ - Side B: BREINER, EGON, 1982 December 31; 1983 January 7 (Cassette 216)
  - LEDERER, FRANZ, 1982 December 31 (Cassette 217)
  - LEDERER, FRANZ, 1982 December 31 (Cassette 218)
  - LEDERER, TOM, 2006 December 8 (Cassette 219)
  - LEDERER, WALTHER - Interview with Tom Lederer about his father, 2006 December 8 (Cassette 220)
  - LEDERER, WALTHER - Interview with Evelyn Lederer about her own work and her husband, Walther, 2007 September (Cassette 221)
  - LEE, EVERETT, Undated (Cassette 222)
  - LEHR, DAVID, 1991 February 22 (Cassette 223)
  - LEHR, DAVID, 1991 February 22 (Cassette 224)
  - LEHR, DAVID, 2007 January 5 (Cassette 225)
  - LEHR, DAVID, 2007 May 7 (Cassette 226)
  - LENEL, FRITZ - Interview with Julia Lenel about her father, Fritz., 2005 June 5 (Cassette 227)
  - LESCHNITZER, ADOLF - Interview with Maria Leschnitzer about her husband, Adolf., 1984 January 23 (Cassette 228)
  - LESER, PAUL - Including material about JULIUS LIPS, lectures on WILHELM GRAEBNER and on the critique of sources., 1983 (Cassette 229)
  - LEVITCH, LEON - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 August 1 (Cassette 230)
  - LEVY, EDWARD - undated, side A. Side B: FALKENBERG, PAUL, 1984 February 12 (Cassette 231)
  - LIEPMANN, KLAUS - Interview with Lise Liepmann about her father, Klaus., 2006 December 4 (Cassette 232)
  - LIPMAN-WULF, PETER, 1986 January (Cassette 233)
  - LIPS, JULIUS, Undated (Cassette 234)
  - LITTAUER, RUDOLF - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 December 31 (Cassette 235)
  - LITTAUER, RUDOLF - Interview with Hilda Littauer about her husband, Rudolf., 2008 April 19 (Cassette 236)
  - LUNAU, HEINZ - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1990 March 30 (Cassette 237)
  - LUNAU, HEINZ - Interview with Elizabeth Marum about her husband, Heinz Lunau, 1991 April (Cassette 238)
  - LUSTIG, LUDWIG, 1988 January 29 (Cassette 239)
  - LYNN, FRED, 1982 November 24 (Cassette 240)
  - MAGNER, MARTIN - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 13 (Cassette 241)
  - MAIER, JOSEPH, 1996 June 11 (Cassette 242)
  - MAINZER, OTTO, 1990 November 28 (Cassette 243)
  - MALKIEL, YAKOV, 1988 August 18 (Cassette 244)
  - MANASSE, ERNST MORITZ, Undated (Cassette 245)
  - MANASSE, ERNST MORITZ, 1991 April 17 (Cassette 246)
  - MANASSE, ERNST MORITZ - Graveside Ceremony at Maplewood Cemetery, Durham, NC, 1997 May 15 (Cassette 247)
  - MARCU, VALERIU - Interview with Eva Marcu about her husband, Valeriu, by Prof. Ulrich Froehlich., 1981 June 23 (Cassette 248)
  - MARGOLIUS, HANS - Interview with Edith Margolius about her husband, Hans. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 February 15 (Cassette 249)
  - MARTIN, THOMAS - Interview with Ruth Martin about her husband, Thomas. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 March 29 (Cassette 250)
  - MARTON, GEORG - Interview with Hilda Marton about her husband, Georg, 1981 December 29 (Cassette 251)
  - MARTON, GEORG - Interview with Hilda Marton about her husband, Georg, 1981 December 29 (Cassette 252)
  - MARTON, GEORG - Interview with Elizabeth Marton about her brother, Georg, 1982 January 29 (Cassette 253)
  - MARX, JOSEF and ANGELINA - side A. Side B: HEINSHEIMER, HANS, 1984 March; Undated (Cassette 254)
  - MARX, HENRY, 1991 February 22 (Cassette 255)
  - MARX, HILDE - Interview with June Kaplan about her mother, Hilde Marx. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 August 10 (Cassette 256)
  - MAURY, KURT, Undated (Cassette 257)
  - MAYER, ALFRED - Interview with Peter Mayer about his father, Alfred., 2006 December 17 (Cassette 258)
  - MAYER, MANFRED, Undated (Cassette 259)
  - MAYER, PETER, 2006 December 17 (Cassette 260)
  - MELAMID, ALEXANDER - Interview with Ilse Melamid about her husband, Alexander., 2009 May 5 (Cassette 261)
  - MICHAEL, FRANZ - Interview with Ingrid Osterhaug about her father, Franz Michael., 2008 February 27 (Cassette 262)
  - MICHAEL, WALTHER P. - Memorial service for Walther P. Michael at Ohio State University., 1986 January 15 (Cassette 263)
  - MICHAEL, WOLFGANG - Interview with Marion Michael about her husband, Wolfgang., 2005 June 26 (Cassette 264)
  - MICHAEL, WOLFGANG - Interview with Hubert Heinen about colleague, Wolfgang Michael., 2009 March 24 (Cassette 265)
  - MICHAELIS, KURT - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 December 27 (Cassette 266)
  - MIERENDORFF, MARTA, Undated (Cassette 267)
  - MILAKOWSKI, HERMANN, Undated (Cassette 268)
  - MNNIG, HANS - Interview with Gertrud Mnnig about her husband, Hans, (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1989 December 30 (Cassette 269)
  - MNNIG, HANS - Interview with Hans Mnnig about his father, Hans, 1997 November 1 (Cassette 270)
  - MORTON, FREDERIC, 1979 October 27 (Cassette 271)
  - NATHAN, HELMUTH - interview with Mrs. Nathan about her husband., Undated (Cassette 272)
  - NATHAN, OTTO - Interview with Herman Starobin on Nathan., 1991 February 5 (Cassette 273)
  - NEBENZAHL, SEYMOUR - Interview with Harold Nebenzal about his father, Seymour Nebenzahl. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 May 17 (Cassette 274)
  - NECHELES, HEINRICH - Interview with Stefanie Necheles about her husband, Heinrich. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 16 (Cassette 275)
  - NELSON, EVA and HERBERT, Undated (Cassette 276)
  - NEUBAUER, PETER BELA, Undated (Cassette 277)
  - NEUMANN, ALFRED - Interview with Selma Neumann about her husband., Undated (Cassette 278)
  - NEUMANN, FREDERICK, Undated (Cassette 279)
  - NEUMANN, ROBERT - side A. Side B: NEUMANN, FREDERICK, 1983 August 26 (Cassette 280)
  - NEUMANN, ROBERT, Undated (Cassette 281)
  - NEUMANN, SIGMUND - Interview with Eva Jane Fridman about her father, Sigmund Neumann., 2008 April 9 (Cassette 282)
  - NIEDERLAND, WILLIAM G., 1982 November 7 (Cassette 283)
  - OESTE DE BOPP, MARIANNE - Interview with Peter Bopp about his mother, Mariann Oeste de Bopp, 2006 May 29 (Cassette 284)
  - OPPENHEIMER, JOHN - Interview by Prof. Ulrich Froehlich., 1981 June 23 (Cassette 285)
  - OSWALD, RICHARD - Interview with Gerd Oswald about his father, Richard, side A. Side B: ULMER, EDGAR, 1983 January 9; Undated (Cassette 286)
  - OSWALD, RICHARD - Interview with Shirley Ulmer about her husband, Edgar, Undated (Cassette 287)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Radio (WABD) interview, December 16, 1957, 1957 December 16 (Cassette 288)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Dictating a letter to Heinz Gollong, Undated (Cassette 289)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interview on arming Europe, Undated (Cassette 290)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interviews with H. Ascher and Gerold Jeremias on Paetel, Undated (Cassette 291)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interviews with H. Ascher and Gerold Jeremias on Paetel, Undated (Cassette 292)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interviews with H. Ascher and Gerold Jeremias on Paetel, Undated (Cassette 293)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO, 1981 January 31 (Cassette 294)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interviews with Heinz Gruber and Rudolf Schwarz on Paetel, 1981 May 21 (Cassette 295)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interview with Max Wehling on Paetel, Undated (Cassette 296)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interview with Lisl Paetel about her husband, Karl O. Paetel, 1978 March 8 (Cassette 297)
  - PAETEL, KARL OTTO - Interview with Lisl Paetel by Franz Wehage, 1981 (Cassette 298)
  - PAL, GEORGE - Interview with Zsoka Pal about her husband, George. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 28 (Cassette 299)
  - PAPPENHEIM, ELSE, 1991 February 23 (Cassette 300)
  - PAPPENHEIM, FRITZ - Interview with Ivonne Pappenheim about her husband, Fritz, 1991 July 20 (Cassette 301)
  - PAPPENHEIM, FRITZ - Interview with family friend, David Rasmussen, 2006 February 19 (Cassette 302)
  - PAPPENHEIM, FRITZ - WBAI broadcast, "If This Be Reason", Undated (Cassette 303)
  - PHIEBIG, ALBERT - Interview with Marianne Phiebig about her husband, Albert., 2006 February 15 (Cassette 304)
  - PLANT, RICHARD, 1974 December 5 (Cassette 305)
  - POPPER, FELIX - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 November 16 (Cassette 306)
  - POPPER, FREDERIC - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 December 27 (Cassette 307)
  - PRAWY, MARCEL - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 February 26 (Cassette 308)
  - PROSKAUER, ERIC, 1984 March 22 (Cassette 309)
  - RATHAUS, KAROL - Interview with Gerta Rathaus about her husband, Karol, side A. Side B: WANGH, MARTIN, 1984 March; Undated (Cassette 310)
  - RAUBITSCHEK, ANTONY - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 17 (Cassette 311)
  - REINHARDT, GOTTFRIED - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 May 18 (Cassette 312)
  - REISCH, WALTER - Interview with Lisl Reisch about her husband, Walter. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 May 1 (Cassette 313)
  - REMAK, H. H. H., 2004 May 4 (Cassette 314)
  - REUNING, KARL - Interview with Elsie Reuning Fox about her father, Karl Reuning (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1990 February 23 (Cassette 315)
  - REUNING, KARL, 2006 November 9 (Cassette 316)
  - RICH, MARTIN - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 November 2 (Cassette 317)
  - RICHARDS, RICHARD KOHN - Interview with Erika Richards about her husband, Richard, 2001 March 13 (Cassette 318)
  - RICHTER, HANS - side A. Side B: JASNY, NAHUM., Undated (Cassette 319)
  - RIEDERS, FREDRIC - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 December 22 (Cassette 320)
  - RIESENFELD, ALPHONSE - Interview with Heidi Oliva about Riesenfeld. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 August 11 (Cassette 321)
  - RIESENFELD, STEPHAN - Interview with Prof. Richard Buxbaum on Riesenfeld., 2000 February 28 (Cassette 322)
  - ROHRLICH, GEORGE, Undated (Cassette 323)
  - ROSENBERG, HANS REINHARD - Interview with Rebecca L. Rosenberg about her husband, Hans, 1983 August 29 (Cassette 324)
  - ROSENBERG, MARY, 1982 January 30 (Cassette 325)
  - ROSENHAUPT, HANS - Interview with his former secretary, Judith Pinch., 2006 December 8 (Cassette 326)
  - RUBEL, NOMI, 1990 November 18 (Cassette 327)
  - RUDEL, JULIUS - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1989 November 4 (Cassette 328)
  - RUDOLF, MAX, Undated (Cassette 329)
  - RUDOLF, MAX - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1989 June 19 (Cassette 330)
  - RUDOLF, MAX - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), On one Side B: FRENKEL, STEFAN, 1990 (Cassette 331)
  - RUEDIGER-LITTLEJOHN, FINI - Interview with Bill Littlejohn about his wife, Fini., 2007 September 5 (Cassette 332)
  - RUNES, DAGOBERT - Interview with Regeen Najar about her father, Dagobert Runes., 2006 January 11 (Cassette 333)
  - SAHL, HANS - "Memoiren eines Moralisten"., Undated (Cassette 334)
  - SALINGER, ALFONS - Interview with Rosalie Salinger about her husband, Alfons., Undated (Cassette 335)
  - SCHABER, WILL, 1979 August 1-1979 October 5 (Cassette 336)
  - SCHACHTEL, ERNST - Interview with Zeborah Schachtel about her husband, Ernst, ca. 2005 July 2 (Cassette 337)
  - SCHACHTEL, ERNST - Interview with Zeborah Schachtel about her husband, Ernst, 2009 April 14 (Cassette 338)
  - SCHACHTEL, ERNST - Interview with Zeborah Schachtel about her husband, Ernst, 2009 April 14 (Cassette 339)
  - SCHANZER, GEORGE - Interview with George Schanzer about his life and work., 2009 December 15 (Cassette 340)
  - SCHATZKI, WALTER - Interview with Michael Schatzki about his father, Walter., 2009 June 3 (Cassette 341)
  - SCHEIN, MARCEL - Interview with Hilde Schein about her husband, Marcel. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 August 23 (Cassette 342)
  - SCHILDKRAUT, JOSEPH - Interview with Leonora Schildkraut about her husband, Joseph, (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), side A. Side B: LEBORG, REGINALD, 1984 June 12 (Cassette 343)
  - SCHILLER, NORBERT - Interview with Judith Sutcliffe and Mary Schiller (widow) about Norbert Schiller. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 July 23 (Cassette 344)
  - SCHINDLER, RICHARD - Interview with Bella Schindler about her husband, Richard. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 January 4 (Cassette 345)
  - SCHLENK, FRITZ - Interview with Edward Schlenk about his father, Fritz., 2005 June 4 (Cassette 346)
  - SCHMIDT, ERICH - Interview by Franz Wehage., 1981 January (Cassette 347)
  - SCHOENBERGER, GUIDO - Interview with Walter Heiman about his father-in-law, Guido Schoenberger., 2009 June 9 (Cassette 348)
  - SCHOENFELD, ALICE - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 May 9 (Cassette 349)
  - SCHOENFELD, ELEANORE - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 May 9 (Cassette 350)
  - SCHRAG, KARL - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 March 27 (Cassette 351)
  - SCHRAG, PAUL - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 March 26 (Cassette 352)
  - SCHULMAN, GERDA, 1991 February 13 (Cassette 353)
  - SCHULTZ, HEINZ - Interview with Margarete Schultz about her husband, Heinz., 1984 April 5 (Cassette 354)
  - SCHUR, HANS - Interview with Helen Schur about her husband, Hans., 1991 March 2 (Cassette 355)
  - SCHUSCHNIGG, KURT - Interview with Kurt von Schuschnigg, Jr. about his father, Kurt., 1984 June 5 (Cassette 356)
  - SCHUTZ, ALFRED - Interview with Ilse Schutz about her husband, Alfred, side A. Side B: RADO, SANDOR. Interview with Peter Rado about his father, Sandor, Undated (Cassette 357)
  - SCHWERIN, KURT, ca. 1990 (Cassette 358)
  - SECKEL, HELMUT - Interview with Margaret Seckel about her husband, Helmut. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 August 22 (Cassette 359)
  - SERGER, FREDERICK (FRITZ [FRYDERYK] SINAIBERGER) - Interview with Helen Serger about her husband, Frederick., 1986 April 2 (Cassette 360)
  - SGALITZER, GEORGE - Interview with Norma Andreadis about her father, George Sgalitzer, 2008 June 29 (Cassette 361)
  - SGALITZER, GEORGE - Autobiographical taperecorded at the request of H. Thomas Jr. for a project on the history of Hwamei Hospital in China, ca. 1980s (Cassette 362)
  - SGALITZER, GEORGE - Interview with Jonathan Hillyer about his uncle, George Sgalitzer, 2006 (Cassette 363)
  - SGALITZER, GEORGE - Oral history interview, conducted by Gerald Faris, 2006 May 22 (Cassette 364)
  - SGALITZER, GERDA - Interview with Nitra Hillyer about her mother, Gerda Sgalitzer., 2009 June 12 (Cassette 365)
  - SILBER, HANS, Undated (Cassette 366)
  - SILBER, HANS - Interview with Thomas Silber about his father, Hans. Also on tape: NEUMANN, ROBERT, 2007 September 27 (Cassette 367)
  - SILBERMANN, ISIDOR, 1984 June 29 (Cassette 368)
  - SIMHA, ROBERT, 2004 May 6 (Cassette 369)
  - SIMONS, HANS, Undated (Cassette 370)
  - SINGER, ROLF - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 August 21 (Cassette 371)
  - SIODMAK, ROBERT - Interview with his brother, Curt Siodmak. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 7 (Cassette 372)
  - SLOTTA, KARL - Interview with Maja Slotta about her husband, Karl. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 February 15 (Cassette 373)
  - SLOTTA, KARL - Interview with Sabine Crozier about her father, Karl Slotta., 2008 January 14 (Cassette 374)
  - SOLMSEN, FREDERICK - Interview with Elisabeth Solmsen about her husband, Frederick., 1991 April 18 (Cassette 375)
  - SOLT, ANDREW - Interview with George Solt about his brother, Andrew. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 May 18 (Cassette 376)
  - SORELL, WALTER, 1982 February 27; 1982 March 6 (Cassette 377)
  - SPIEGEL, SIEGMUND - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 April 3 (Cassette 378)
  - SPIRO, EUGEN - Interview with Lilli Spiro about her husband, Eugen., 1984 June 21 (Cassette 379)
  - SPRANGER, OTTO - Interview with Rose Spranger about her husband, Otto. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 April 3 (Cassette 380)
  - SPRINGER, BERNHARD J. - Interview with Ursula Springer about her husband, Bernhard., 1984 March 29 (Cassette 381)
  - STAUDINGER, HANS - 89th birthday, 1978 (Cassette 382)
  - STEIN, KURT - Interview with Sigrid Schneider., Undated (Cassette 383)
  - STEINITZ, FRANZ - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 August 22 (Cassette 384)
  - STEINITZ, HANS - Interview by Lucy Steinitz of her father, Hans., 1978 November 23 (Cassette 385)
  - STEINITZ, MARTHA, Undated (Cassette 386)
  - STEINITZ, ROBERT - Interview with Lore Steinitz about her husband, Robert, and her aunt, MARTHA STEINITZ, 2000 July 6 (Cassette 387)
  - STEINITZ, ROBERT - Interview with Michael Steinitz about his father, Robert, 2000 July 12 (Cassette 388)
  - STIEBEL, ERIC - Interview with Gerard Stiebel about his father, Eric., 2006 November 6 (Cassette 389)
  - STIEFEL, ERNST - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 December 28 (Cassette 390)
  - STOERK, HERBERT - Interview with Elizabeth Stoerk about her husband, Herbert., 1991 March 22 (Cassette 391)
  - STOESSINGER, JOHN - Autobiography, partly told, partly read by Stoessinger., 2007 September 2 (Cassette 392)
  - STONE, KURT - side A. Side B: SPERLING, OTTO, conclusion of interview, 1984 March 23 (Cassette 393)
  - STRASFOGEL, IGNACE - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 December 23 (Cassette 394)
  - STRATTON, HENRY M. - Interview with Jutta Grosser on Stratton., 1984 July 5 (Cassette 395)
  - STRAUSS, BRUNO, Undated (Cassette 396)
  - STRAUSS, HANS - Interview with Elizabeth Strauss about her husband, Hans. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 January 4 (Cassette 397)
  - SYMONETTE, LYS - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 November 13 (Cassette 398)
  - TARG, ROSLYN, 1982 January (Cassette 399)
  - TAUSSIG, WALTER, 1982 December 16 (Cassette 400)
  - TEICHNER, HELMUT - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 August 23 (Cassette 401)
  - THAN, JOSEPH - Interview with Marina Than about her husband, Joseph. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 May 24 (Cassette 402)
  - THIELE, WILHELM - Interview with John Thiele about his father, Wilhelm. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 2 (Cassette 403)
  - THOEREN, ROBERT - Interview with Richard Weininger on Thoeren., Undated (Cassette 404)
  - TISCHLER, HANS - Interview about himself and his brother, KURT TISCHLER (pseud. Kurt Maury)., 2004 May 4 (Cassette 405)
  - TISCHLER, KURT, Undated (Cassette 406)
  - TOLLER, ERNST - Interview with Steffi Black on Toller, 1980 January 1 (Cassette 407)
  - TOLLER, ERNST - Interview with EVA WALTER on herself and on Ernst Toller, 1983 August (Cassette 408)
  - TOLLER, ERNST - Interview with George Sutro on Toller, 1994 May 30 (Cassette 409)
  - TOLLER, ERNST - Interview with Aline Valangin about Ernst Toller., 1981 August (Cassette 410)
  - TOLLER, ERNST - Zeit zum Zuhren. In Sachen Riedel/Guala. Ein Schweizer Mordprozess vor 50 Jahren. Discussion of case used by Toller as a basis for his play Die blinde Gttin., Undated (Cassette 411)
  - TORS, IVAN - Interview with Erwin Tors about his brother, Ivan. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 June 6 (Cassette 412)
  - ULMER, EDGAR, Undated (Cassette 413)
  - UNGAR, FREDERICK - Interview with Ruth Selden on Ungar, 1991 February 12 (Cassette 414)
  - UNGAR, FREDERICK - Interview with Hansi Ungar about her husband, Frederick, 1991 February 13 (Cassette 415)
  - VALE, EUGENE - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 April 15 (Cassette 416)
  - VAN EYSS, OSSO, Undated (Cassette 417)
  - VERNON (Whl), MANFRED, 2000 March 2 (Cassette 418)
  - WAELSCH, SALOME, Undated (Cassette 419)
  - WALDMAN, FREDERIC - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 November 14 (Cassette 420)
  - WALLACH, HANS - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1997 August 1 (Cassette 421)
  - WALTER, EVA, Undated (Cassette 422)
  - WALTER, OTTO LUDWIG - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 January 3 (Cassette 423)
  - WANGH, MARTIN, Undated (Cassette 424)
  - WANGH, MARTIN, 2008 April 25 (Cassette 425)
  - WASSERMANN, FRIEDRICH - Interview with Franz Wassermann about his father, Friedrich. - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1989 September 16 (Cassette 426)
  - WEIL, ROLF - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 August 21 (Cassette 427)
  - WEINSCHENK, FRITZ - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1990 April 4 (Cassette 428)
  - WEINSCHENK, FRITZ, 2007 July 12 (Cassette 429)
  - WEITZMANN, KURT, Undated (Cassette 430)
  - WEITZMANN-FIEDLER, JOSEFA - Interview about PAUL FRANKL (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1990 April 5 (Cassette 431)
  - WEITZMANN-FIEDLER, JOSEFA - Interview about her and her husband, KURT WEITZMANN, 1991 February 15 (Cassette 432)
  - WERFEL, FRANZ - Interview with Gustave O. Arlt on Werfel., Undated (Cassette 433)
  - WERNER, ERIC, 1982 December 15 (Cassette 434)
  - WICCLAIR, WALTER - Interview with Marta Mierendorff on Wicclair., 1984 June 22 (Cassette 435)
  - WILK, GERARD, Undated (Cassette 436)
  - WILK, GERARD - Interview with Susan Wilk about her husband, Gerard, 2002 April 20 (Cassette 437)
  - WINTER, GEORGE - Interview with Anne Winter about her husband, George., 1984 March 17 (Cassette 438)
  - WIRTH, OTTO, 1983 January 1 (Cassette 439)
  - WITTKOWER, RUDOLF - Interview with Margot Wittkower about her husband, Rudolf., 1982 December 6 (Cassette 440)
  - WHL, MANFRED, Undated (Cassette 441)
  - WOLFF, REINHOLD - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee)., 1990 February 15 (Cassette 442)
  - WOLFF, VICTORIA, Undated (Cassette 443)
  - WOLLHEIM, KURT - Interview with MONA WOLLHEIM about her and her husband, KURT., 1982 November 26 (Cassette 444)
  - WRONKOW, LUDWIG, 1981 March 11 (Cassette 445)
  - WRONKOW, LUDWIG, 1981 March 11 (Cassette 446)
  - WRONKOW, LUDWIG - Memorial held at Goethe House, NY, October 26, 1982, 1 cassette., 1982 October 26 (Cassette 447)
  - WUTHENAU, ALEXANDER VON - Interview with Tito von Wuthenau about his father, Alexander, 1995 January 1 (Cassette 448)
  - WYLER, JULIUS - Interview with Eva Wyler about her father, Julius., 2006 March 2 (Cassette 449)
  - WYLER, WILLIAM - Interview with Margaret Tallichek Wyler about her husband, William (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1989 May 9 (Cassette 450)
  - ZADOR, EUGENE - Interview about Eugene Zador by family members (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1989 September 2 (Cassette 451)
  - ZASSENHAUS, HERBERT - Interview with Peter Zoll about Zassenhaus., 2007 November 2 (Cassette 452)
  - ZERNIK, CLEMENTINE, 1991 February 5 (Cassette 453)
  - ZIPPER, HERBERT - (recording made by Dr. Eve Lee), 1989 October 3 (Cassette 454)
- Photographs, Undated; 2
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - List of exhibit photographs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - A-Bomb, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Kurt Herbert Adler, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Josef Albers, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Martha Albrand, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Franz L. Alt, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Gnther Anders, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 8)